# RAQUEL ZUECO

Student of Masters in International Business with Modern Languages

### CONTACT INFORMATION

350 Cathedral Street, G2 1BQ, Glasgow

Email: raquelzueco6@gmail.com

Tel.: +34 691070128

### BACKGROUND

I am a student in International Business with Modern Languages at Strathclyde University, although currently I'm completing my year abroad in Toulouse Business School. This has provided me with varied and good linguistic abilities alongside a solid resolve and consistency in my work. My ability to adapt has been developed greatly through the experience of living in three different countries and learning to embrace diverse cultures.

## LANGUAGES

**SPANISH** Mother Tongue

**ENGLISH** Fluent Written and Spoken (Level C2/Proficiency)

**FRENCH** Good Command, Written and Spoken (B2 Certificate, lived a year in France)

#### INTERESTS

**MUSIC** ABRSM Piano exam Level 3 and Music Theory Level 3. Performed in numerous recitals.

**TRAVEL** Organised a city tour experience as part of Travel and Tourism course. Have completed over 500km in hikes through Spain and travel abroad often.

**ART** Took over 10 years of art classes, developing skills in design, watercolour, oil paint and pencil.

# **EDUCATION**

MASTERS IN INTERNATIONAL BUSINESS WITH MODERN LANGUAGES University of Strathclyde, Glasgow | 2019-2024

**Subject Focus:** Marketing, Human Resource Management, International Management and French.

YEAR ABROAD IN FRANCE Toulouse Business School | 2022-2023

**Subject Focus:** Brand Activation, Marketing of Wine, Wine Tourism, Wine Culture and Image and Video Marketing.

# **EXPERIENCE**

SOCIAL MEDIA CONTENT CREATOR | Curious Marketing | Sept. 2021 - May 2022

Created educational and engaging content for a Marketing Consultancy start-up posting on Instagram, Facebook and LinkedIn. Used Canva to create weekly and monthly content.

SEASONAL SALES ASSISTANT | Tienda Solidaria Piel de Mariposa Patraix | June 2022 - Aug. 2022

Responsible for store organization, assisting customers and taking payments. Additionally, was in charge of the window exposition design and store promotion to existing clients.

# ADDITIONAL SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE

**MODEL UN** Participated in two Model UN Local Conferences where I represented the political interests of two different countries. This experience involved taking part in debates, which improved my ability to communicate ideas clearly and negotiate.

**AIESEC** Took part in the initiative for 3 months, in which as part of a team we promoted teaching internships abroad by creating all marketing collateral and promotional stands.

**Fête des Vendanges** Participated in the second edition of this event in Capitol Square in Toulouse, where we sold wine tasting kits to participants. Link to an article about the <u>event</u>.

**Wine More Time** Helped organise a wine tasting event with unusual wines from the South-West region, where we had to contact and secure rare wine varieties ourselves from commercial wine suppliers.

**Master Level Programme South of France** Have attained this certification demonstrating my knowledge of the wines in the Languedoc – Roussillon region equivalent to 2-3 level of WSET (Wine Spirit Education Trust in London). <u>Link here.</u>